{
    "subject": "resource/Agile_software_development",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Agile software development",
    "human_readable": "The label of Agile software development is Agile software development.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9256212115287781,
            "question": "What label is used to describe Agile software development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7861163020133972,
            "question": "Is Agile software development a type of methodology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6856645345687866,
            "question": "What are some common tools used in Agile software development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6467218399047852,
            "question": "What are the main benefits of using Agile software development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6381165981292725,
            "question": "Who benefits from using Agile software development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.612427294254303,
            "question": "How does Agile software development differ from traditional software development approaches?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5730596780776978,
            "question": "What is the role of collaboration in Agile software development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5703011155128479,
            "question": "Can Agile software development be applied to projects of all sizes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5075780153274536,
            "question": "What are the different stages or phases involved in an Agile software development project?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5010756254196167,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a principle followed in Agile software development?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Agile software development is Agile software development.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1587_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the different stages or phases involved in an Agile software development project?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1587_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can Agile software development be applied to projects of all sizes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1587_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the role of collaboration in Agile software development?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1587_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1587_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1587_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1587_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1587_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1587_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1587_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1587_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1587_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1587_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1587_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents provided contain multiple references to \"Agile Software Development\" as a methodology, approach, and term used in software development. The information supports that \"Agile Software Development\" is indeed the label for this whole idea, and it is not another name or incorrect term."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe phrase \"It\u2019s really about thinking through how you'll understand what\u2019s occurring within the environment that you\u2019re in today, identify what uncertainty you\u2019re facing, and work out how you'll adapt thereto as you go along.\" from one of the documents supports the statement that the label \"Agile\" reflects the adaptiveness and response to change in Agile software development. Therefore, the information provided in the context does support the triple \"The label of Agile software development is Agile software development.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}